# **Kobiljon Toshnazarov**

1201, 100 High-Tech building Inha-ro, Nam-Gu Incheon South Korea

+8210 5034 2705 kobiljon@nsl.inha.ac.kr linkedin.com/in/gobiljon

# **OBJECTIVE:**

A challenging software engineering position that deeply utilizes algorithms and critical thinking (i.e., Android/iOS Software Engineering, Web Back-End Engineering, Microservices Engineering, etc.)

#### SUMMARY:

Gained exposure to key concepts of Computer Science and Engineering as a graduate researcher in the Networked Systems Lab<sup>1</sup>. Also, prior to graduate school, gained professional experience in industry by working as a Software Engineer in IUTLab<sup>2</sup>, and conducting a club of programmer students in Inha University in Tashkent.

## SKILLS / KEYWORDS:

- C++ (from 98 till 17), Kotlin, Java (7, 8), Python, C#, SQL
- Git, Docker, gRPC, Linux Kernels, OS proficiency (Mac OS, Windows, Linux), Adobe Photoshop, Latex
- Algorithms (problem solving), Microservices, Django (REST APIs), Ionic (TypeScript)
- Confidence, Time management, Focus, Friendliness and manners, Work ethics, Public speaking, Research

#### **EDUCATION:**

- Bachelor's Degree, 2018, Computer Science and Engineering (GPA 3.42 / 4.5), INHA UNIVERSITY in Tashkent (IUT), Uzbekistan
- Master's Degree, 2020, Computer Science and Engineering (GPA 3.86 / 4.5), INHA UNIVERSITY, Incheon, South Korea

#### **EXPERIENCE:**

Graduate Research Assistant, Networking Systems Lab in INHA University, South Korea, full-time 2018-Present Involved in research projects:

- EasyTrack (conference MobiSys 2019) a large scale sensor data collection platform for researchers
- <u>MindForecaster</u> (conference CHI 2020) mobile application to help users prepare for stressful events using personalized interventions
- IMSP (conference KICS 2020) an intelligent mobile sensing platform for automatized abnormal behavior detection
- EDD, <u>SNMP/GOOSE</u> KERI<sup>3</sup> network failure monitoring platform, in collaboration with KERI (outsourced project)
- 오늘하루 A cognitive behavioral therapy program to improve various psychological difficulties (outsourced project)

Lecture Assistant in INHA University, South Korea, part-time 2018-2019

- Conducted laboratory courses for Application Programming in Java (201802CSE2107001, and 201901CSE2107001)
- Conducted laboratory courses for ComputerNetworks (201902CSE4202001)

Software Engineer, IUTLab Tashkent, Uzbekistan, part-time 2016-2017

- Developed Android and Windows client applications (i.e., <u>Kadrlar</u>, <u>MindWind</u>, etc.)
- Used tools C#, Java, Maven, PostgreSQL, Git, Firebase, Android Studio, Eclipse, Microsoft Visual Studio

PC & Mobile Phone Repair Assistant Technician, Kashkadarya Uzbekistan, part-time 2009-2011

- Repaired mobile phones (hardware and software)
- Did OS installations (Windows XP)
- Assembled / disassembled PCs and mobile phones

#### LANGUAGE SKILLS:

English - fluent (active IELTS 7.5 / 9)

Russian & Uzbek - bilingual (native)

Korean - intermediate (able to conduct non-complex conversations)

### **PUBLICATIONS:**

- EasyTrack Orchestrating Large-scale Mobile User Experimental Studies (2019), MobiSys'19 Proceedings
- IMSP an Intelligent Mobile Sensing Platform for Automatized Abnormal Behavior Detection (2020), KICS Winter Conference 2020 Proceedings
- Toward Future-Centric Personal Informatics: Expecting Stressful Events and Preparing Personalized Interventions in Stress Management (2019), CHI'20 Proceedings

<sup>3</sup> Korean Electricity Research Institute

-

<sup>&</sup>lt;sup>1</sup> nsl.inha.ac.kr (INHA University, South Korea)

<sup>&</sup>lt;sup>2</sup> iutlab.uz (Tashkent, Uzbekistan)